[bright music]
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Velvet fang with a
glitch in the groove ♪
♪ Goldfish brain but I never lose ♪
♪ Side-eye sharp got a cyclone mood ♪
- Hey, baby.
- This is for you.
- That's good. Thank you.
♪ Hologram pulse with ♪
♪ a peppermint [indistinct] ♪
♪ Mirror talk slick, I don't do plain ♪
- I just came to get this,
so I can get my day started, you know?
- Mm. Thank you.
Oh, can you please stop by
the store on your way home?
I will, but I got meetings back to back.
- You know I got you [indistinct]
- Okay.
- All right, I love you, I'm out.
- Mm, me too.
- Be good. All right.
- You too.
- [Darren] Keep that body safe, baby.
[indistinct]
- My husband, baby.
[upbeat music]
[upbeat music continues]
Okay, Crystal, yes,
I'll remember to tell them
to move their trash cans
back to the backyard.
[doorbell chiming]
Hey Crystal, I'll call you back.
Yes, how may I help you?
- Yes, I'm here to see Darren.
- [Trina] And who are you?
- I'm his brother.
[intense music]
- Man. What?
There you go brother.
- Man, thank you bro.
- Thank you [indistinct]. Baby.
- But I thought you told me
that Davon.
- Trina,
that's what they told me.
- So he didn't really die?
- I'm right here.
What she talking about, bro?
- This...
- I don't know. This just seems crazy.
It just doesn't make any sense.
- I know. Caught me by surprise too.
How did you find me?
- Man, this chick I used to mess with,
she worked at the
attorney general's office.
She could possibly find anybody, bro.
- Yeah, I guess women
could work for the FBI, right?
- [Devon] Yeah, man.
- So what now?
- Hey, I guess you got a new brother.
- What? Man, I always
wanted a sister, bro.
- Yeah, sir.
Man. So you remember everything?
Did you take notes or something?
- Yeah, bro.
Every little thing, man.
- So tell me, you on this side of town?
- Yeah, man, you know I stay
about 15, 20 minutes from here.
- Oh, okay. That means you're close.
You gonna have to stop by more often, man.
We have a lot of time to
catch up on what we lost.
- Man, already, bro.
You know I got you, man.
- [Darren] All right, I'm
gonna leave y'all two.
I gotta use the restroom.
Baby. Behave, all right.
- [Devon] Good food.
- Thanks.
So prison?
- What about it?
- What really happened in there?
Darren was told that his
brother had an accidental death.
- You see that was the man.
They hate to see a Black
man come out on top.
They tried to keep me away
from my successful brother.
- Oh, okay.
Well speaking of, do you remember
Darren running for senator
while you were locked up?
- [Devon] Of course I do.
- Oh.
- He won the senator, right?
- Man, he lost because
of his law-breaking brother.
[muffled radio chattering]
- Driver, out of the car!
Driver, out of the car now!
[intense music]
- Man, baby brother.
I hate to have to cut this short man,
but it's been a long day, man.
- All right, nah man, it's cool bro.
I understand, man.
- But you going to come
through tomorrow though, right?
- Yeah, for sure.
What's your number?
- Oh yeah, man.
Gotta have that.
Come on, bro.
Thank you for stopping by anyway, man.
There you go.
[indistinct]
- [Devon] That's cool, bro. Yeah.
- [Darren] All right, baby.
- See you, sister. Nice meeting you.
- Likewise.
- Man, baby brother. I'm still tripping,
but I'm glad you found me, man.
- Yeah, me too, bro.
- And I'm still real
sorry about that, okay.
- Man, come on.
You good, bro. You gotta chill out, man.
We passed that shit,
all right.
- All right.
You take care of yourself,
all right?
- All right, man,
you too, bro.
- All right.
- What?
- For real, Darren?
- For real, Darren. What?
- Your brother out of nowhere
who you thought was dead.
- Yeah, and?
- And you don't think
that's a little weird?
- No. Should I?
- Yes. And why the hell not?
He just miraculously shows
up at your front doorstep.
- I mean, I guess they must
have made a mistake, right?
- What?
- Yeah, they were wrong.
And now he's here and
I have my brother back.
Baby, look, I guess I must have missed him.
I mean, and I didn't quite realize it
until I didn't have to.
All these years, I missed him.
- Baby, come here.
Come here, baby. I'm so sorry. I'm sorry.
I got you. I promise. I'm so sorry.
[birds chirping]
- Hey man, where the fuck you at?
Oh, you got me fucked up, girl.
I don't need to fucking relax.
Hurry up and pull the fuck up, man.
We just talked about this shit!
The fuck is wrong with you?
[birds chirping]
- [Darren] You know, baby.
- [Trina] Mm.
- I really thank you for supporting me
through all of this, you know.
I really can't thank you enough.
- Always, baby. It's just me and you.
- And now Devon,
let me get up outta here so I can get done.
- Yeah, can we please just make
sure the files are correct?
Okay, I appreciate that.
Thank you.
Mhm-hmm, yep.
And enjoy your day.
And that, ladies and gentlemen,
is what we call happy hour.
You know what, I don't know who you are,
but I know who you are not.
[birds chirping]
- Trina!
Hey, girl.
- Hey, Crystal, what's up?
- Look, that guy who was
at your house last night.
Well, he sure was doing
a whole lot of yelling
to whoever he was on the
phone with before he left.
- He was?
- Yeah.
You don't think I would lie
about something like that.
- Girl, no, it's just he claims
that he's Darren's brother.
- Oh, okay. A family reunion.
- No. Hell no.
Look girl, he lying and I know it,
but I just, I got no proof.
- Huh? Proof.
Okay, let me see what I can find out
about Mr. Mystery man.
[gentle music]
- Yeah, because if you could do that,
that would really help me out.
- Mhm-hmm, there he is now.
- Look, Crystal, I'll talk
to you later, all right.
[indistinct]
I'm gonna call you.
I'm sorry. Are you lost?
- Did I do something wrong?
- You can't just show up
to our house without asking first.
- Asking who?
I texted Darren.
I can't come see my brother?
- Your brother?
He's working late, okay.
- Even better. Give us more
time to get acquainted.
He know I'm here.
Just look at this shit.
So your living home, bro.
And your girl.
We always wanted one of these.
Okay, bro, you know we always wanted
a fucking fireplace.
Man, I guess we couldn't
get that kind of shit.
Bro, living [indistinct] now, huh?
Look at this shit, man. Wow.
Oh, here we go, look at this shit.
Ain't that cute?
I see you, bro. Y'all look happy.
- We are.
- Yeah. Man, wow!
You made it, bro.
She's beautiful. Who's...
- [Trina] Don't touch that.
- That's cool.
This might be somebody I know, right?
'Cause you know I've been gone
so this...
- Don't touch that either!
- Whoa. What you don't
trust me or something?
- I don't even know you!
- That's fair.
Ain't nothing gonna happen to you.
- Ain't that usually what people say
right before something happens to 'em.
- You know Darren
always did like 'em smart.
Oh yeah, who's that gorgeous
woman you was talking to?
- Crystal, our neighborhood watch lady.
And she's nosy,
and she could find out
anything about anybody.
All we have to do is call her.
- Oh yeah?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- I think you need to come
back when Darren gets home.
- I think I should stay.
- I think you...
Hey baby.
- Hey woman.
- Hey.
- How you?
- Always good.
I miss you. How was work?
- It was long
and hot out there.
- Yeah.
- How was your day?
- It was good.
How was your day?
- It was cool. You okay?
- Yeah.
Baby.
- What?
- Bro, what's up man?
You all right?
- How you doing?
- I came to see you.
You tell me I can stop by.
- Yeah. Everything okay?
- Yeah. Remember you told me
I can always come see you.
Anytime.
- Right.
I tell you what, man.
[indistinct]
Go on out to the patio.
I'm gonna grab us a few beers.
We got a lot of chopping up to do.
Okay?
- Yeah.
You right about that bit, man.
[indistinct]
- He pop...
- I'll talk to you later.
- [TV anchor] Ryan
[indistinct] come out swinging.
We'll have to wait a
minute or two for the offense
to get out here…
- Beautiful night, dawg.
- Yeah it is, man.
You looking good too, baby brother.
- Appreciate that bro.
Been on that road, man. Huh?
- Yeah man.
When you start smoking though, man?
- Man, just a little bad habit I picked up.
- Yeah, for sure.
- You feel me?
- How you get out early again?
It was like 17 years, you know?
What is was a felony in
possession of a firearm, correct.
- Good ass lawyer, man.
- [Darren] Ah.
- Had to get rid of the old
motherfucker, you know.
- Hey dawg, listen, you saved my life man.
You sacrificed yours to give me a chance.
Man, I can't even begin to thank you dawg.
I don't even know where
start to repay you man.
But when I found out
you passed away in prison,
oh my god, bro!
Listen man,
- Hey, hey, hey, hey man.
Look bro, chill out man.
Right, look dawg, I get it.
We got a lot of catching up to do, man.
- That indeed, man.
I'm talking fishing trips,
visiting mom and dad grave site,
and fixing up this damn house, man.
We gotta do that.
Yeah, for real.
- Yeah man, look, I can help
with everything.
- [Darren] Yeah.
- Start learning how to fix shit,
you know.
- What?
- [Devon] Yeah man.
- You?
- [Devon] Down that road, bro,
I learned to do a lot of shit though.
- Okay, well we gonna start you
with something real simple, man.
The treadmill upstairs,
I can't figure out what
to do with that shit.
Start with that.
- Yeah, I got you.
I'll look into that shit for you.
- Thank you.
- [Devon] You working out,
ain't it boy?
- Come on man.
What, you went stupid?
Look at your boy, man. Come on now.
Or did you forget that too?
- Man, you ain't do shit for real, boy.
- You know bro.
- Now I'm talking, my bad bro, my bad.
- Hey, just to be real though, man.
That shit is for the wife, bro.
She use that way more than I do, bro.
That's why I need you
to fix it for her, man.
- Got you bro.
- [Darren] Thanks man.
- I can check [indistinct] for you.
- [Darren] I appreciate that.
- Damn man!
Look at you bro, big ass house man.
Good ass fucking job, beautiful wife.
- Yeah, I'm blessed bro.
Very blessed man,
but you know how long you been out, man?
You know, what you going
to do now that you home.
You know, I'm digging the new look.
Never thought you'd do
anything with your hair though.
I mean, besides everything bro,
you look like a whole new person.
- Appreciate that bro.
Damn, 21 questions, huh?
- Ah.
- Look bro. I get it man.
I had hella questions too if I was you,
but I'm home.
That's all that matter, right?
- Yeah. That's all that matter, man.
Hey man, this still
don't feel real, brother.
- I know, bro. Feel like
we ain't lost no time,
man.
- I know.
- Actually a lot of time has passed.
- Hey brother, that's my cue, man.
You be safe, all right.
- All right man, you too bro.
God, come on man.
I'll walk you.
- Hey look sis,
you have a good night.
- [Trina] You too.
- I'ma walk you out, man. [indistinct]
All right, be safe boy.
- [Devon] All right, bro.
[indistinct]
[police sirens wailing]
- So you really gonna
act like this is normal?
- Again, Trina, he's my brother!
- You don't know that.
He just waltz in here,
and I feel like he's watching everything.
Even Crystal says something about him.
- Wait, Crystal does
that with everybody, okay!
Listen, he's trying.
So can we just please try too?
- Just promise me that you will be careful,
and don't let him back
into your life so quickly.
- Whatever you...
I'm going to bed, okay. Behave.
[chirping]
- Okay, mystery man.
Let's see if we can find
out who you really are.
[Crystal screaming]
[intense music]
[intense music continues]
- What the fuck?
[intense music]
[intense music continues]
[thud]
[intense music]
No, no! [sobbing]
[Trina sobbing]
- Hey, baby.
Yeah, I know.
Yeah, I don't know how that thing fell.
- [Trina] I don't know either.
- But look, you know
I'm there for you, right?
Tree? Trina, what's our rule baby?
Please don't make me repeat myself.
- [Trina] Transparency.
- That's my girl. So talk to me.
- [Trina] I've been
thinking about this thing
with him just showing up and.
- Okay. Not this again.
- [Trina] I'm serious.
You don't even know anything about him.
And it's been years since you've seen him.
- Well, it doesn't matter.
We are going to meet up again,
and we're going to hang out
and have all the time in the world
to catch up on what we lost.
- [Trina] Baby, I just
want you to be careful.
- I know.
- [Trina] Can we at least make sure.
He's really your brother?
He looks so different from the photos.
Hello?
- All right. So what do you want me to do?
- [Trina] I don't know.
Maybe a DNA test or something.
- So walk up to him and be like, what's up?
Hey bro, you good? Bet.
We need to take a DNA test.
You mean like that? Huh?
- [Trina] No, that's silly.
Not like that, but I dunno,
you'll figure out how to bring it up.
It won't be a problem if
he has nothing to hide.
- All right, I'll ask him
the next time I see him.
- [Trina] Okay baby.
Well, get back to work. And I love you.
- I love you too.
- Hey, what up dawg?
- So I guess you just forgot
we in the corporate office, right?
- Man, ain't nobody forget,
these ugly folks don't care about nothing
that doesn't include the words
county and expeditiously.
- Man, Rich, what you want?
- Oh yeah.
So I heard you on the phone with your girl.
- Wife.
So you been ear hustling.
- Ear hustling sounds so
messy, and I ain't messy.
You know that's them boys
up there on the fifth floor.
- Rich.
- All right. All right.
So I couldn't help to overhear
that you got this fake brother
that you need a DNA test for.
- [Darren] Man, he's...
- Wait a minute,
let me finish.
I can help you with that.
- [Darren] Oh yeah?
- Yeah, man,
I got a cousin down to work at the LBG.
They be doing DNA tests all the time.
I can hit her up.
- All right, bet. Thank you.
But I'm gonna need you to quit listening
in on my conversations, okay?
- Hey, just call me curiosity.
You know I killed the cat too.
- Get out.
- All right, man. Damn.
I just be trying to look out
for your black ass, man.
- I appreciate it.
[upbeat music]
Baby. Hey baby.
Hey, hey, wake up.
There she go.
How you?
- I must have dozed off.
- You did, it's okay.
Hey, if you're too tired,
we don't have to do nothing tonight.
- Tonight?
- Yes, tonight. Remember?
- Oh, shoot. I forgot,
we got reservations.
- Hey, but it's totally up to you, okay?
It's up to you.
- What?
- Yeah.
- No, I still wanna go.
I'm gonna just finish some
things with my presentation
and then I'm start getting ready.
- Okay, well in that case,
I'm gonna go take a shower
and wait for you to get ready.
- Good.
- Okay.
- Let me get up.
- All right, you do that.
- Baby, did you see Crystal on your way in?
- No. And I'm not complaining either.
Now, come on.
- [Trina] You play too much.
- Hmm hmm. You good?
[indistinct]
- Make sure that, drag you to save.
[indistinct] You better go girl, mm.
Why are all these popups here?
Freaking close, close.
No more popups. Thank you.
[indistinct]
Oh...
- Hey. You good?
- Yes. I think this is the one.
- Oh, so my baby gonna get that promotion?
- She sure is.
- That's what I'm talking about, girl.
Hold on baby, you need to go shower girl.
- Ah, jerk.
- I know, right?
All right. It's gonna be a good day.
[gentle music]
[notifications chiming]
[alarm beeping]
[upbeat music]
[indistinct]
[upbeat music continues]
- Damn!
[upbeat music]
[upbeat music continues]
[muffled indistinct whispering]
[indistinct]
[suspense music]
- Come on, I know you [indistinct]
motherfucking code, man.
Fuck. Ah, yeah.
The one time on my pop ups, there we go.
Yeah, motherfucker, I got you now.
Hell yo.
[notifications chiming]
[keyboard clattering]
Save that shit now.
Got your ass.
- [Trina] Thank you baby.
- [Darren] Oh God.
- God, I'm so full.
- Hey, that food was good though, no lie.
- My feet hurt.
- Nah, for real.
The hell?
- What the hell?
What are you doing here?
Are you crazy?
- I thought he would've told you.
- Told me what?
- Yeah, babe, that's my fault.
Davon was in the area
to come fix the treadmill,
like we talked about, right.
So I just gave him the code
since we were already on our way.
- You did what?
- You heard him.
Davon, come on now.
- [Devon] Yeah, my bad bro.
My bad.
- The code to our house?
- It's all right, baby.
He's family.
- Family?
- Yes!
- How did he even get here? What?
- I don't know.
- Okay. Well, you just let him
in the house, you don't
even know how he got here!
- [Devon] I Ubered.
- Oh, he Ubered.
There we go.
Answered right, we okay?
- You and your family have a great night,
'cause I'm going to bed!
- Babe.
- Don't forget what we
discussed earlier, Darren!
Good night.
- Babe, babe!
- You wanna get outta here real quick.
- Don't think we got a choice now, do we?
- Come on, man.
- You buying too man.
Get outta here man. Brothers.
[bright music]
[indistinct]
What's up? You good bro?
She was talking about back there?
[indistinct]
What?
- All right, look, I'm gonna
keep it honest with you D,
and I believe in my heart who
you say you are, all right.
But just to be sure, think
we can get a DNA test?
I know it sound weird.
- What a DNA test?
Hey, come on bro.
What you think somebody could
really be out here pretending
to be your brother, man?
What it Trina ain't it?
- Look, a lot has changed D. That's all.
- All right, bro.
We can do that shit.
Let's do it.
- My man.
You sure?
- Man together for life, bro.
- All right, big dawg.
Let's do it.
- All right guys,
if y'all can look at the slides I pulled up
from the PowerPoint for Q4.
Hold on a second.
Sorry y'all, I don't think my computer
had coffee this morning. Sorry.
- Take your time Mrs. Nelson.
- Come on. Why's it…
It's just not pulling up.
- Okay Mrs. Nelson,
do you think we should just
reschedule this meeting
for a later time?
- Sure. Team, I'll send everybody
the PowerPoint via email.
I'm sorry for the inconvenience y'all.
- What we'll do is we'll reschedule,
try to clear your calendars probably
for next week on Wednesday.
And I'm gonna give you 45
minutes back to your day to today.
Is that all right?
You guys, go ahead and log off.
Mrs. Nelson, can you
stay on for me please?
- Yes sir.
- [Mr. Hale] Thank you.
Have a good day everyone.
- Yeah. Davon Nelson.
[indistinct]
Let me get that for you.
- Woo. Hey woman,
something smell real good.
Hey Trina, guess who I
ran into after work today?
- Let me guess, a distant cousin this time.
- Somebody better than that.
- What up sis?
- I told you it was somebody better.
- I don't know what happened
today, but I will find out.
- [Darren] Trina.
- [Devon] It's cool.
- Dinner's ready.
You can bring it to the table.
- So Trina, how was work today?
- Just fine.
- Darren said you had an important meeting.
How'd that go?
- To be honest with you, I
would rather not talk about it.
- Boss gave you grief, huh?
You know, I hate motherfuckers
who don't appreciate
hard working [indistinct].
You feel me?
- Did they appreciate the
hardworking effort you put
into making license plates?
- Trina!
- It's cool bro.
Don't worry about it.
- Hey baby brother, why the
long face man. You good?
- Look man. That's what
I'm actually here to talk
to you about.
- Okay. Talk to me.
- Landlord selling property
I'm staying at right now, man.
I gotta be out by the weekend.
Look, I just need a couch to
crash in for a few weeks, bro,
until I find me a new spot, you feel me?
- Of course, you do.
- Hey man, you said
all that to say that to me,
you can stay here as long as you need, man.
- Darren!
- Man, bro, thank you man.
Wow bro!
Look man, you know I
appreciate you bro. For sure.
It's only for a few weeks, man.
- Next time say less than that.
You family.
- Yeah, family.
Thank you bro. Hm.
[engine revving]
[treadmill whirring]
[Trina breathing heavily]
[Trina screaming]
- You need to talk to
him about the treadmill.
- Okay, I will talk to him
about the treadmill, okay.
- Okay. But Darren, I need to talk to you
about something else.
- Hey, it's gonna have to wait.
I'm late for the appointment, okay.
- But when you finish,
can you call me please?
- I will. Okay.
- Thank you.
Okay, you have a good day.
- [Darren] Bro, really?
- Man, what bro?
- The treadmill.
- Shit what happened? Damn.
[indistinct]
- So your DNA results will be
in between 24 and 48 hours.
We already got your information,
so we'll email you the
results when they come back.
- Okay, sounds good.
- Like I said, no problem.
- Yeah, but how accurate is this test?
- [Receptionist] It is 99.99.
- Okay, all right.
- No sweat bro.
- Thank you. Thank you.
- You know I got you.
- [Darren] All right.
- Look, I got you, all right.
Appreciate it.
[birds chirping]
[engine revving]
- Hey baby.
Hey. Hey baby. Rich is calling me.
Let me give you a call back, okay?
I love you. I love you.
Hey, what's going on Rich, my man?
[indistinct] Just made it to the house, baby.
Trina, not this shit again!
- Baby, I just have a feeling
that something isn't right.
- What do you got against my brother?
- Nothing. My intuition is telling me
that something is off with him.
- Trina!
- Darren, I'm sorry,
but I'm gonna say it right now.
I feel like he had something to do
with my presentation messing up.
- What? So why haven't you said
anything about this before?
- You right, Darren.
Maybe I should have said something earlier.
- [Darren] Yes.
- Okay. But he's always here.
When was I gonna get
the opportunity to tell you?
- You're tripping. You are tripping, okay!
Please stop. Stop! God!
- Darren, if I'm tripping,
it's because it's hard to
believe he's who he says he is.
- [Darren] Well guess what, Trina?
- [Trina] What?
- When those DNA test results come back,
showing that he's 99.99% my
brother, you are going to relax,
and you're also going to accept the fact
that he's your brother too.
Understand? Understood. Thank you.
- Darren!
Shit!
No.
- Who is on that phone?
- I'm just…
[door bell chiming]
- Oh shit, I'll get it.
- [Darren] Yeah, sure. Get our door bro.
- Damn, bro, give me a [indistinct] man.
- My God.
- [Devon] What's up baby?
- [La-A] Hey daddy.
- Hey.
Been waiting to see your [indistinct].
Hey, act right when you go in here.
- Who is this?
- Bro, Trina,
this is my little boo.
- La-A.
- [Devon] Yeah. La-A.
- Yeah.
- La-A, this is my bro Darren.
And this is my sis, Trina. AKA Tree.
- Ooh Tree.
Like a tree house?
- [Devon] Come on. [indistinct]
- No.
- Oh, well dang, my bad sis.
- And I'm not y'all damn sis.
- Okay!
- [La-A] Oops, she rude.
- Hold on.
It's really nice to meet you, Lala.
- La-A. La-A, La-A.
- All right.
- I need a drink.
- Hey baby, while you
at it, can I get a beer too?
- And another beer.
What you want to drink, stink?
- Oh Daddy, you be rhyming this shit.
Spitting bars, but ooh,
y'all got some [indistinct]
- [Trina] I'm sorry, some what?
- Oh, okay.
I know what you're talking about.
- Champagne. You know
the fancy bubbly stuff.
Girl, I know y'all ain't
got this big ass house
and you don't know what Champagne is.
That's that light skinned shit.
- That's what the fuck I said.
- What y'all watching? Tubi?
- Yeah, like Tubi shit,
but you know they had to put them on game.
They like to watch that white people shit.
- Babe, hurry up with
that beer please. Lord.
- We gotta put them on.
- The cham what?
[indistinct]
- Champagne!
Pour me up a glass!
- That shit crazy.
[muffled chattering]
[indistinct]
- Hey. Hey. Trina.
- [TV anchor] What do you need, Rico?
- Come on, time for bed.
Come on.
- Damn, y'all leaving already?
- Yeah man, we got a meeting
with the bed and we late.
All right.
[indistinct]
- Y'all over there.
- [Darren] Hey man,
see you tomorrow brother.
- Yeah man, go to sleep over there.
- [Darren] Come on baby.
- See you sis.
- Goodnight.
- [Darren] Respect my house, man.
- Man, come on bro.
It's like my shit.
What you taking about?
- Nice to meet you again Lala.
- It's La-A.
- This shit right, bro.
[indistinct]
- [TV anchor] If you stay,
I'll make it worth your while. [indistinct]
[indistinct]
- [TV anchor] My nigga, if you want peace,
[engine revving]
- Crystal, have you found anything out yet?
Girl, call me back.
- Hey sis.
- [Trina] Shit!
- Damn sis, my bad.
- No. Oh no, no.
- Trina. Trina.
[indistinct]
Trina, you good?
- No.
- Everything straight we
heard something falling.
- Well I'm good,
but little Miss scaredy
cat here didn't know
that I was still here.
- I sure didn't. Darren.
- Bro, common courtesy, man.
If you going to have
guests, please let us know,
especially if they're
overnight guests, bro.
Please.
- My bad bro. My bad.
- Thank you. Anything else sis?
- Yes. Actually, you...
- And please do not be
drinking directly from the jug.
- Oh.
- It's a little too late
for that.
- Y'all don't do that?
- What?
- Oh.
- Look, relax, we joking man.
We joking.
[indistinct chattering]
[notification chiming]
- [indistinct]
Oh [indistinct]
- What?
- Yoh,
- 99%.
- [together] 99.99%.
- Match.
- [indistinct] I told you.
- I knew it.
- I knew it!
- I knew it all along,
I just wanted to respect
what y'all wanted, bro.
- Meet me out back, man.
Meet me out back
because it's official, man.
- [Devon] It's official.
[indistinct]
I told you. [indistinct]
- I'm gonna go put my swimsuit on,
daddy.
- I like that girl.
Hey La-A, we got
something to celebrate girl.
With your fine ass.
Yeah, this shit official.
[bright music]
[water splashing]
- Whoo! Should've get Nemo
in this motherfucker.
[bright music]
♪ I feel you watching me ♪
♪ Pull up across the room ♪
♪ I think you like the view ♪
♪ You gonna make a move ♪
♪ I don't make this easy for you ♪
- [Darren] Man, your girl good, man.
- I got you one too brother-in-law.
- Thank you sister-in-law. Yeah.
- [La-A] Hey sis.
- So, feel good right?
Back to normal man.
Just like you never left.
- Man, normal be pushing it.
Life been good bro. Real good.
- Funny it doesn't seem normal to me.
- Trina!
- No Darren, I mean it!
He just shows up here
out of nowhere like a ghost,
sleeping under our roof.
No real answers, just
trust me, I'm your brother.
- And yet here I am, living,
eating, drinking wine with you.
That's good enough ain't it?
- You know, I think it's super dope.
Two brothers reunited from the dead.
Ooh, like the "Lion King."
- "Lion King!"
- It's just like the "Lion King," man.
- Well it's crazy because this
isn't a fairytale, sweetie.
It's real life and people just
don't come back from the dead
without some kind of scars or something.
- Oh, I got scars.
In just a place you can't see.
- And to that, I say we
family, broken or not.
- To family, resurrected and shit.
Yeah...
- Ah, here we go.
Hey baby brother.
Tonight was good, right?
I ain't laugh like that
in a long time, man.
- Yeah bro.
Felon has a way of
sneaking back into your life
when you least expect it.
- Some snakes aren't welcome.
- Don't worry, Trina.
I'll never do anything to hurt Darren.
You know, maybe me
and you should get closer,
so you can get to know the real me.
- See Trina, we gonna be
big ass happy family in no time.
- It's all love.
- My man.
Baby, put these up for me.
- You know, your
brother is like really sweet,
and I think it's kind of
cute how y'all look alike.
- You know [indistinct], you talk too fucking much.
- Well, that's what you
like about me daddy.
- I like when you don't talk
much, you don't think too hard.
Keep it that way and just do your job.
People who disrupt
the plan won't last long.
Get some fucking rest.
You got a big day tomorrow.
[intense music]
- [Mr. Hale] Okay, so
maybe you don't know,
well, let me enlighten
you just for a second.
Corporate received an
email early this morning,
threatening to leak
information about the company
and when they traced the IP address,
can you tell me whose
computer it came back to?
- I mean, not mine.
Wait.
- [Mr. Hale] It came back
to yours, Trina!
- Okay, sir, wait a minute.
There is no way that
anything like that can come
from my computer.
I, I don't even know what
you're talking about.
[indistinct]
- [Mr. Hale] You know what's sad?
I'm sitting here in this office
waiting on your presentation
and then I get this news instead from HR.
I'm just...
I just wanna know why.
Why would you do it?
- I'm just confused
because I was still working
on my presentation, but then
Darren's brother popped up
outta nowhere and I was dealing
with that and I was dealing
with work and it's just a lot
on my plate right now, sir.
- [Mr. Hale] I see. Well,
let me take something
off your plate.
I have to inform you
that we're relieving you
of your position effective immediately.
- What?
- [Mr. Hale] Without pay?
Yes ma'am!
At least until the
investigation is complete,
and then you are cleared
in the investigation.
- Mr. Hale, please.
- [Mr. Hale] No, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no.
I've said enough and I've heard enough.
You are gonna get some paperwork from HR.
I'll follow up with you
in a couple of weeks.
That's the end of discussion.
- What's up y'all,
it's your girl La-A.
- Yeah, it's her.
Meat on the cheek. [indistinct]
- Bro, get your girl.
Tell her to come outside.
- Gimme this.
- Why you grabbing my meat?
Give my meat back.
- Hey man.
Whoa, whoa, bro, come on.
- You play too much.
- Hey.
- Uh-uh.
- [Trina] So I guess you
got off work early, huh?
- Hey babe. Yeah I did.
- So you couldn't call, text,
stop by the office? Nothing.
- Okay. Hold up, to my defense,
I was gonna do that.
But you've been so crowded at work lately,
I did not want to disturb you.
- Okay, no problem.
Don't let me stop the fun.
Y'all go ahead, you, Davon and Lasha.
Y'all have all the fun
y'all want.
- Uh-uh, I told her, [indistinct]
my name is La-A.
- Trina!
- It's not that hard.
You getting out the pool?
[indistinct]
- Ah bro.
- She be ruining everything.
- Hey sissy.
- That's all right.
- It's all right, baby.
- It could just be you and me,
baby.
- Hot tub, yeah.
- Mhm-hmm.
- Don't say nothing. Don't say nothing.
[indistinct]
- Baby, what's going on?
Why would you just leave like that?
Hmm?
- What you talking about?
- I mean, why would you
just walk off tripping and shit?
Come on. Come on.
- So you out there flirting
with this whole Lasha,
but I'm doing something wrong.
- Flirting?
- Yes.
- First of all, nobody was flirting, okay.
And secondly, her name is La-A.
Say it with me, La-A, okay.
- I'm not saying that shit.
- You impossible.
- Y'all out here playing in
my face, frollicking and shit.
You come here all dripping wet,
messing up my nice ass floors.
What is going on, Darren?
- Woman, woman, woman, woman.
- Really? What's with you?
- Listen to me. I'm gonna
go shower and cool off,
and forget any of this shit ever happen.
And I suggest, and I mean,
highly suggest that you do the same.
Understand? Understood. Thank you.
- Darren, I'm tired of all
these strangers in my house!
It's okay.
[indistinct]
[intense music]
[indistinct] Shit!
- Sorry, I didn't mean to scare you.
- Well, you did.
- Look, you know I'ma be around
for a long time though, right?
- If you say so.
- I know you don't like me.
You made that clear since day one.
But what I also noticed,
you ain't been able to
keep your eyes off me.
Just be honest.
Deep down inside,
you wish it was me
instead of Darren, don't you?
- Ugh. I could never.
- You could if you would.
- Oh, stop!
Why would you do that?
- [indistinct] Tastes good.
See why bro wife'd you up.
I wonder what else tastes good on you.
- But my husband.
- Yeah, I can't tell.
- You better not.
You better, if you ever say
one word to Darren about this,
I promise if you do it, I...
- Or what?
I tell you what, you stop
trying to come between me
and my brother and I'll consider it.
Nice cake.
[cellphone vibrating]
[notification chiming]
[La-A moaning]
[la-A moaning]
[water dripping]
[intense music]
[Trina panting]
[Trina moaning]
[notifications chiming]
[gentle music]
[gentle music continues]
[cellphone ringing]
- [credit union] First Dibs Credit Union.
- Hello? Yes. This is Trina Nelson.
I need to check my account.
- [credit union] Okay.
Account number and password?
- Yeah. 1, 2, 3, 7, 8, 9. Family first.
- [credit union] All right, gimme a moment
while I pull up your account.
All right. Account showing
it's zero balance, ma'am.
- I'm sorry, it must be
some kind of mistake.
Can you check again?
- [credit union] Ah, sure. Absolutely.
Okay. Yep, still at a zero balance, ma'am.
- Yeah, no, I'm sorry.
It must have been my husband.
I'll speak with him about it.
- [credit union] All
right. Have a great day.
- Okay, thank you.
[engine revving]
[chirping]
Shoot. Crystal, it's Trina.
You know your door is open.
Crystal, I haven't heard from you,
I just want to check on you.
Did you forget to take your trash out?
Crystal! Oh shit.
Crystal.
[Trina screaming]
[suspense music]
Baby. Here baby.
- What up, sis?
- [Darren] Hey baby.
- Darren, I just left
Crystal's house. She's dead.
- Oh no.
Yeah, there's a lot of that
going on around here lately.
- Look, Darren, can I please
speak with you privately?
- I mean, what's good is it going to do?
I mean, anything you can say to me,
you can say in front of my brother.
- Dammit! Darren, he is not your brother!
- This again.
- Okay, I'm sorry I didn't,
I didn't mean to yell.
He is not Davon, Darren.
I don't know who he is, but that's not him.
- But the DNA test results,
I mean kind of say he's 99.99% a match.
- Yeah, 99.99%.
- Okay, well did you talk to Richard
because he said something
is wrong with the test!
- And how do you know about that?
- [Trina] [indistinct] I saw the text when
he text your phone, baby.
- So you went through my phone.
- Darren, listen, I don't
know what's going on.
All I know is this man is not Davon.
I don't know who he is,
baby, but he is not him.
- [Devon] And just how you know that?
- Darren,
I know this might
not sound right and baby,
I honestly don't know
how you gonna take it.
I've been meaning to tell
you that Davon is really dead.
- Man, come on with the bullshit. Trina!
- What? What? It's the truth!
And he's not who he says he is!
- Again! How do you know that?
[indistinct]
- [Trina] I just know.
- Nobody just knows, Trina.
They actually need proof.
You got any proof?
- [Devon] Yeah Trina,
do you have any proof?
Oh yeah, you got plenty of that, don't you?
Like that time you went
up there to see him in jail.
Yeah, he told me all about that visit.
Oh, let's not forget,
I watched [indistinct] plenty of letters
and I don't think Darren
received one of them.
What happened to those letters, Trina?
Wanna talk about that?
I think you got all the proof. Yeah.
- I...
- I, I...
You, you what?
Oh, this shit gonna be fucking good.
Well, sis, I mean Trina,
since you can't tell bro here
the reason how you
know I'm not the real Davon
is because you the one responsible
for Davon's fucking death.
Oh shit, that's not it.
She cheated on you in
your own fucking crib at that.
Man, hold on. Yeah, look at this shit.
[indistinct]
Look, you won't tell my
secret, I won't tell yours.
- Please, it's not like this.
So just listen, please.
[indistinct]
- Listen. Oh, he listening.
Tell him, tell him how you
took away the only person
that really loved him away from him.
Tell him!
- Baby, I love you.
- (chuckles) Be a woman and tell him,
tell him how you had somebody on the inside
to make sure he'll never come home again.
Didn't you, didn't you?
- Trina, Tree, did you?
Did you?
- I did what I had to do.
They, Darren they weren't
supposed to kill him.
I just made a phone call
to have him transferred,
so he wouldn't have
contact with you anymore.
What would've happened, Darren?
You were running for office.
What if they would've found out
that your brother was a convicted felon,
and he took the rap for you!
It was a disaster waiting to happen.
Making your name look bad, making a mess!
All I wanted to do is
clean it up for you, baby.
- Oh, you had my brother killed!
- He, he wasn't supposed to die!
- But he died 'cause of you!
They told me how he begged for mercy.
I remember that fucking night.
I was supposed to
protect him, but I didn't.
I was his cellmate, his only friend.
And we favored so much,
everyone thought we was brothers.
I watched 'em drag his limp body out.
I swore I wouldn't rest
until I avenge his death,
and make whoever did it
suffer just like Davon suffered.
[intense music]
[intense music continues]
- So you, you knew, you
knew this whole time that I knew
that you weren't really Davon.
- Yep. But I'm what's left of him now.
- I can't even lie though, bro.
Even past the physical shit,
it really is something totally
different about you, man.
- About that.
- Bro. What?
- Ah, man, man.
Man, I'll tell you later.
[indistinct]
Watching this game, bro.
- [indistinct]
That was nice man...
- Bro, that's actually what
I'm gonna talk to you about.
- What's good?
- Look, you write a lot
here has changed, bro.
I'm not Davon, my real name's Trevor.
[indistinct]
Look. Hold up.
Hold on, ain't what you think, man.
We did time together, bro.
We was close.
That's part of what the reason I'm here.
- Man, what the fuck?
- Look bro. I know, I
know. Look, I got you.
Davon was a good dude, bro.
He used to always say we can be twins, man.
- So what's the other reason you here?
- Man, your wife ain't
really who you think she is.
- You see Trevor here.
- [Trina] Trevor?
- Yeah, that's Trevor.
Nice for y'all to get acquainted.
He told me everything
and you mother fucker,
ruined my family.
You took my brother away
from me!
- [Trina] No.
- My brother blood is
on your fucking hands.
And you supposed to make me believe
that all of this shit was for me.
- Yes, because,
Darren, I, I love you.
Baby and I'm sorry, but I just did
what I thought was best.
Every, everything I did, every lie,
every secret, baby, I did it for us.
Think about it, please.
- I assure you that there will
never be another us again.
You make me sick to my fucking stomach,
even when I found out!
I just wish you knew
how much I enjoyed
ruining your fucking life.
I hate you!
- Thank God, La-A is
smarter than what she look!
She dug up every fucking thing.
You ready?
- I've been ready.
- Ready for what? Darren?
Oh Darren!
- Beg now, right bitch!
I'm going to enjoy making you suffer
just like my brother did!
- [Devon] This look familiar to you?
- So fucking evil!
- And what the fuck does that make you?
Go Trina, head start.
Let's see if I still got it.
- Darren.
- Three.
- [Trina] This isn't you, baby!
- Two!
- [Trina] Don't do this,
Darren.
- Okay, one!
[Trina screaming]
[indistinct]
- One more.
[gunshot firing]
[Trina sobbing]
- All right, hey listen,
you go do your thing.
I'm gonna catch up with
you after I give my statement
to the police, all right.
- Hey look bro, if it came down to it,
Davon would've did the
same thing for me and you.
- I know, I already know that man.
I just feel so fucking guilty
for all that time he did
for me on the inside.
You know, I should have
fucking visited...
- Hey, hey man,
look, it's not your
fucking fault, it's hers.
Like Davon always say, bro,
sometimes you gotta lose everything
to get what the fuck you want.
[indistinct] Bro.
- Go.
- Darren, Darren help.
- You know, I'm sure Davon was begging
for his life with his last breath too.
You know, I'm glad Trevor
found out who you really were,
and told me, him and
Davon were really close.
- Thank you for looking out for me.
I got you for life, bro.
- Darren, look.
Darren.
[Trina gagging]
[Devon VO] Sometimes
you have to lose everything
in order to have exactly what you want.
[suspense music]
- [Darren] You know.
- Huh?
- We only got about a few more minutes.
[Trina mumbling]
till you bleed out and
succumb to your wounds.
You see, honestly, I wasn't
even going to kill you at first.
I was just gonna make
your fucking life suffer.
Oh shit, I almost forgot.
[Trina moaning]
[Darren grunting]
and three, two,
one, lift off.
Yo man, what you doing still here, man?
You gotta go now.
It was my gun that put Davon in there, man.
I chose my career.
- Nigga, you chose you.
- And what did you choose?
- The blood [indistinct], I chose my brother.
- My man.
Get outta here, man.
I got it from here.
[indistinct]
- You too.
And thanks.
♪ Don't be afraid of the dark ♪
♪ Be careful with stars ♪
♪ Not every light is gonna guide it baby ♪
[indistinct police radio]
- [police radio] Shots
fired at a private residence. [indistinct]
Spouse advised as the suspect,
but the scene, GSW victim
is 35-year-old Trina Nelson.
Victim was DOA.
♪ In the morning, it's all gonna vanish ♪
♪ Don't be afraid of the dark ♪
[indistinct police radio]
♪ Be careful with stars ♪
♪ Not every light is gonna guide you ♪
[indistinct police radio]
♪ Yeah. When I blow up, I'ma
soar high like Peter Pan ♪
♪ And real life be living out my dreams ♪
♪ If I'm waking up ♪
♪ It's in a foreign land ♪
♪ Whole wrist covered up with ice ♪
♪ Dealership, never asked the price ♪
♪ I hit the [indistinct] with my dogs ♪
♪ Y'all swipe it once
without thinking twice ♪
♪ 'Cause this is what I was made for ♪
♪ Man, I know this what I came for ♪
♪ On a big stage, couple thousand people ♪
♪ They do whatever I say so ♪
♪ Have chicks the color of the rainbow ♪
♪ Have chains on me like Django ♪
♪ Be a long way from my... ♪
- [Darren] A vote for
Darren Nelson is a vote
for your future.
My campaign manager,
Trevor and I would like
to thank you Houston. Thank you.
- Thank you for taking my call, detective.
Yes, I have some information
on that Nelson case.
Of course, I'll hold.
[intense music]
[upbeat music]
♪ [indistinct] Bunch of bad bitches ♪
♪ And we ain't saying nada ♪
♪ Pull up in my Benz
in my bag like Prada ♪
♪ Really goin in going ham full throttle ♪
♪ Really thought I wouldn't but I am ♪
♪ What you thought oh, ay ♪
♪ Yeah I'm ballin like nair ♪
♪ Ay and if you fake disappear ♪
♪ Ay you don't want these problems here ♪
♪ Ay we be getting money over here ♪
♪ Feelin' like I'm up one ♪
♪ Thumbin' through these
benji's get you some ♪
♪ Yuh ♪
♪ Feel like I just I just hit the lotto ♪
♪ Can't touch me ♪
♪ I'm untouchable ♪
♪ It's like ♪
♪ Feel like I'm up one ♪
♪ I'm up one yeah aye ♪
♪ Ballin like up one ♪
♪ I'm up one ♪
[indistinct]
♪ You know that I'm up one ♪
♪ I'm up one yeah ay ♪
♪ Get you some ♪
♪ Get you, get you some ♪
♪ Fe fi fo fum ♪
♪ I'm the beta to the drum ♪
♪ 'Kickin' down doors and you know ♪
♪ I'm coming vroom vroom ♪
♪ Better run ♪
♪ If I want it then it's done ♪
♪ Had to pop off cause
they ain't doing none ♪
♪ I ain't going back broke ♪
♪ Stick to the plan ♪
♪ Get the funds ♪
♪ Remember back then ♪
♪ I could not afford the lunch ♪
♪ Now we champagne poppin' ♪
♪ Bubbles at the brunch ♪
♪ Knew that I was gonna make it ♪
♪ I always had a hunch ♪
♪ Ay, lemme make it clear ♪
♪ Are you, are you listening ♪
♪ I been, I been, I been it ♪
♪ I been ballin since a kid ♪
♪ I ain't settling ♪
♪ I move forward when I steer ♪
♪ And I never check the rear ♪
♪ Everything glacier ♪
♪ Lookin for me ♪
♪ I'm up here, really under me ♪
♪ Oh dear, you can catch me if you can ♪
♪ But I bet you won't get near ♪
♪ Got it jumpin' over here ♪
♪ Main character for real ♪
♪ It's [indistinct] evident it's clear ♪
♪ Every year is my year ♪
♪ Feelin' like I'm up one ♪
♪ Thumbin' through these
benji's get you some ♪
♪ Yuh ♪
♪ Feel like I just [indistinct] hit the lotto ♪
♪ Can't touch me ♪
♪ I'm untouchable ♪
♪ It's like ♪
♪ Feelin' like I'm up one ♪
♪ I'm up one [indistinct] ♪
♪ Ballin like I'm up one ♪
♪ You know that I'm up one ♪
♪ I'm up one [indistinct] ♪
♪ Get you some, [indistinct] ♪